drnatura.com 2019-04-06

# Mylan

We collect Personal Data when you:

  * use the Sites and
  * communicate with us.

We also collect information, such as anonymous usage statistics, by using cookies, server logs and other similar technology as you use the Sites.

**Using the Sites** We collect information you post through the Sites. For example, we collect information when you apply for a job, respond to surveys, post comments or pictures on our social media pages, request information from us or otherwise interact with us online or through a mobile application. We will collect the information you provide in such submissions, including any Personal Data.

**Customer Relations** We may collect Personal Data through your communications with our customer relations team.

**Cookies, Automatic Data Collection, and Related Technologies** We collect and store information that is generated automatically as you use the Sites, including your preferences and anonymous usage statistics.

When you visit the Sites, we and our third-party service providers receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, and from cookies and similar technology. We work with third parties, such as widget providers, who may keep track of your browsing activities on this and other websites. Most browsers allow you to block and delete cookies. However, if you do that, the Sites may not work properly.

By using the Sites, you are authorizing us to gather, parse and retain data related to the provision of the Sites, as described in this Statement.

**HOW MYLAN USES YOUR INFORMATION**

We use Personal Data to: 

  * provide and improve our services;
  * communicate with you;
  * respond to your request for information (e.g., to provide refill reminders); and
  * as otherwise required by law, regulation or governmental audit.

We may use Personal Data to create non-personal aggregate information and use such information for any purpose, including for marketing purposes, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

**Internal Business Usage** We use your information, including Personal Data, for internal business purposes and to facilitate the Sites. 

**Communications** We may send email to the email address you provide to us for informational and operational purposes, such as customer service, system maintenance, or to inform you about job opportunities with Mylan (if you have elected to receive such notifications).

**Marketing** We may use your information, including Personal Data, to provide advertising on the Sites and to send you information about our products or services we think may be useful or relevant to you. We may share other data collected by the Sites to enable the delivery of online advertising on the Sites, or otherwise facilitate transmittal of information we think may be useful or relevant to you. Where required under applicable law, we will only perform such marketing activities with your consent

**Aggregate Data** We may de-identify and aggregate data collected through the Sites and use it for any purpose, to the extent permitted under applicable law.

**MYLAN MAY DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION**

We may share your information:

  * with our subsidiaries and affiliates, on a need-to-know basis;
  * with our third-party service providers, to provide services on our behalf;
  * to comply with legal obligations, including in response to lawful requests by public authorities, such as to meet national security or law enforcement requirements;
  * to protect and defend our rights and property; and
  * with your permission.

We do not rent, sell or share Personal Data about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have your permission.

**We Use Vendors and Service Providers** We may share any information we receive with vendors and service providers retained in connection with the provision of the Sites.

**Social Networking and Other Websites** We may allow you to share information, including Personal Data, through the Sites with social networking websites, such as Facebook. We do not share your Personal Data with them unless you direct us to share it. Their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies, and you may be able to modify your privacy settings on their websites.

**As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures** We may access, preserve and disclose your Personal Data, other account information, and content if we believe doing so is required or appropriate to: comply with law enforcement requests and legal process, such as a court order or subpoena; respond to your requests; or protect your, our or others’ rights, property or safety.

**Merger, Sale, or Other Asset Transfers** If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, financing due diligence, reorganization, bankruptcy, receivership, sale of Mylan assets or transition of service to another provider, your information may be sold or transferred as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract.

We may also disclose your Personal Data with your permission.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and protected against unauthorized access, change or deletion. Unfortunately, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

We do not knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information from children under 13 years old, and no part of the Sites is directed to children under the age of 13. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, you may alert us at [communications@mylan.com](mailto:communications@mylan.com). If we learn that we have collected any personal information from children under 13 years old, we will promptly take steps to delete such information and terminate the child’s account. 

**  
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

As a convenience to our visitors, the Sites may contain links to the websites of another company or organization. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred from our Sites and be connected to the website of the company or organization you selected. Our Privacy Statement does not apply when you leave our Sites.

**INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS**

To offer our services, we may need to transfer your Personal Data to countries other than the country in which the data was originally collected, including the United Sates, where we are headquartered.  Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided that information. When we transfer your Personal Data to other countries, we will protect it as described in this Privacy Statement. By providing Personal Data to us, you consent to the transfer of Personal Data to countries outside of your country of residence, including the U.S.

If you are located in the EEA, we comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of Personal Data to countries outside of the EEA.  Mylan Inc. has certified to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce and the European Commission regarding the collection, storage, use, transfer, and other processing of Personal Data transferred from the EEA to the U.S. For more information about the Privacy Shield or see our certification, please see [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). To see a copy of our Website Privacy Shield Policy, please click here.

If you are located in Switzerland, Mylan has implemented an intra-group agreement to cover the transfer of Personal Data between Switzerland and Mylan Inc. 

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You may have the right under applicable law to request access to and receive information about the Personal Data we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Data, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. You may also have the right to object and withdraw your consent to the processing of your Personal Data.

To exercise your rights, please contact us as indicated in the contact information section below. 

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY STATEMENT AND PRACTICES**

We may revise this Privacy Statement from time to time. We will post any adjustments to the Privacy Statement on this web page, and the revised version will be effective when it is posted. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on this page or by sending you an email or other notification.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or if you’d like to exercise your choices or rights, contact us via:

  * E-mail at [dataprivacy@mylan.com](mailto:dataprivacy@mylan.com); 
  * Mail at Chief Privacy Officer, 1000 Mylan Boulevard, Canonsburg, Pa. 15317;
  * Phone: 1-724-514-1800 

If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland, Mylan N.V. is the entity responsible for processing your Personal Data.

Effective Date: Sept. 30, 2016
